<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>test on 基于Jenkins的DevOps流水线实践</title>
    <link>/cont/</link>
    <description>Recent content in test on 基于Jenkins的DevOps流水线实践</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 08:41:44 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/cont/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Archetypes</title>
      <link>/cont/archetypes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cont/archetypes/</guid>
      <description>Using the command: hugo new [relative new content path], you can start a content file with the date and title automatically set. While this is a welcome feature, active writers need more : archetypes.
It is pre-configured skeleton pages with default front matter. Please refer to the documentation for types of page to understand the differences.
Chapter To create a Chapter page, run the following commands
hugo new --kind chapter &amp;lt;name&amp;gt;/_index.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archétypes</title>
      <link>/cont/archetypes.fr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cont/archetypes.fr/</guid>
      <description>En utilisant la commande: hugo new [chemin vers nouveau contenu], vous pouvez créer un nouveau fichier avec la date et le title automatiquement initialisé. Même si c&amp;rsquo;est une fonctionnalité intéressante, elle reste limitée pour les auteurs actifs qui ont besoin de mieux : les archetypes.
Les archétypes sont des squelettes de pages préconfigurées avec un Front Matter par défaut. Merci de vous référer à la documentation pour connaitre les différents types de page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown syntax</title>
      <link>/cont/markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cont/markdown/</guid>
      <description>This page is a shameful copy of the great Grav original page. Only difference is information about image customization (resizing, add CSS classes&amp;hellip;)
 Let&amp;rsquo;s face it: Writing content for the Web is tiresome. WYSIWYG editors help alleviate this task, but they generally result in horrible code, or worse yet, ugly web pages.
Markdown is a better way to write HTML, without all the complexities and ugliness that usually accompanies it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Syntaxe Markdown</title>
      <link>/cont/markdown.fr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cont/markdown.fr/</guid>
      <description>Cette page est une copie de la doc de Grav. La seule différence porte sur la personalisation des images (taille, ajout de classes CSS&amp;hellip;) Pour des raisons évidentes, cette page n&amp;rsquo;a pas été traduites en français 😁
 Let&amp;rsquo;s face it: Writing content for the Web is tiresome. WYSIWYG editors help alleviate this task, but they generally result in horrible code, or worse yet, ugly web pages.
Markdown is a better way to write HTML, without all the complexities and ugliness that usually accompanies it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menu extra shortcuts</title>
      <link>/cont/menushortcuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cont/menushortcuts/</guid>
      <description>You can define additional menu entries or shortcuts in the navigation menu without any link to content.
Basic configuration Edit the website configuration config.toml and add a [[menu.shortcuts]] entry for each link your want to add.
Example from the current website:
[[menu.shortcuts]] name = &amp;quot;&amp;lt;i class=&#39;fab fa-github&#39;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/i&amp;gt; Github repo&amp;quot; identifier = &amp;quot;ds&amp;quot; url = &amp;quot;https://github.com/matcornic/hugo-theme-learn&amp;quot; weight = 10 [[menu.shortcuts]] name = &amp;quot;&amp;lt;i class=&#39;fas fa-camera&#39;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/i&amp;gt; Showcases&amp;quot; url = &amp;quot;/showcase&amp;quot; weight = 11 [[menu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raccourcis du menu</title>
      <link>/cont/menushortcuts.fr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cont/menushortcuts.fr/</guid>
      <description>Vous pouvez définir des entrées ou raccourcis supplémentaires dans le menu sans avoir besoin d&amp;rsquo;être lié à un contenu du site.
Configuration simple Editez le fichier de configuration config.toml et ajoutez une entrée [[menu.shortcuts]] pour chaque lien que vous voulez ajouter.
Exemple pour ce site:
[[menu.shortcuts]] name = &amp;quot;&amp;lt;i class=&#39;fab fa-github&#39;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/i&amp;gt; Github repo&amp;quot; identifier = &amp;quot;ds&amp;quot; url = &amp;quot;https://github.com/matcornic/hugo-theme-learn&amp;quot; weight = 10 [[menu.shortcuts]] name = &amp;quot;&amp;lt;i class=&#39;fas fa-camera&#39;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/i&amp;gt; Showcases&amp;quot; url = &amp;quot;/showcase&amp;quot; weight = 11 [[menu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Icons and logos</title>
      <link>/cont/icons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cont/icons/</guid>
      <description>The Learn theme for Hugo loads the Font Awesome library, allowing you to easily display any icon or logo available in the Font Awesome free collection.
Finding an icon Browse through the available icons in the Font Awesome Gallery. Notice that the free filter is enabled, as only the free icons are available by default.
Once on the Font Awesome page for a specific icon, for example the page for the heart, copy the HTML reference and paste into the markdown content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tags</title>
      <link>/cont/tags/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 08:41:44 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cont/tags/</guid>
      <description>Learn theme support one default taxonomy of gohugo: the tag feature.
Configuration Just add tags to any page:
--- date: 2018-11-29T08:41:44+01:00 title: Theme tutorial weight: 15 tags: [&amp;quot;tutorial&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;theme&amp;quot;] ---  Behavior The tags are displayed at the top of the page, in their insertion order.
Each tag is a link to a Taxonomy page displaying all the articles with the given tag.
List all the tags In the config.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tags</title>
      <link>/cont/tags.fr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 08:41:44 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cont/tags.fr/</guid>
      <description>Le thème Learn supporte une des taxonomy par défaut de GoHugo : les tags.
Configuration Il suffit d&amp;rsquo;ajouter un tableau de tags sur la page :
--- date: 2018-11-29T08:41:44+01:00 title: Tutoriel pour le thème weight: 15 tags: [&amp;quot;tutoriel&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;theme&amp;quot;] ---  Comportement Les tags sont affichés en haut de la page, dans l&amp;rsquo;ordre dans lequel ils ont été saisis.
Chaque tag est un lien vers une page Taxonomy, qui affiche tous les article avec ce tag.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>